<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nashville's Best Real Estate Training - Angie Cody</title>
    <description>Angie Cody, a top Real Estate Agent in Nashville, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. Her Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 15:08:04 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 15:08:04 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Hosting an Open House Is a Great Start to Your Career</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wwgD7g7iHtE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hosting an open house is a great way to get your start in the real estate business if you’re on a limited budget.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/strategy-call/&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/img/cta-images/full-strategy-call.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Strategy Call&quot; class=&quot;full-post-cta&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the best ways to get started in real estate if you have little or no money is to host an open house. To make your open house a success, here are a few tips to follow. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, &lt;strong&gt;pick a house that excites you.&lt;/strong&gt; “Exciting” can mean a part of town you’re passionate about, or a house in a hot price point that you know will generate traffic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, &lt;strong&gt;start promoting the open house three or four days in advance.&lt;/strong&gt; A great way to do this is by putting signs out. I recommend getting two different types of signs for the open house—one that’s branded with your company logo, and another that’s more of the generic, red-and-white kind you can buy at Home Depot or Walmart. If you put out two types of signs, people will think there are two open houses in the same area, and they’ll be more likely to drive by. You’ll want to put out anywhere from 10 to 20 signs, and they should be on every street corner leading up to the open house. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=To make your open house a success, here are a few tips to follow.%20http://localhost:4000/why-hosting-an-open-house-is-a-great-start-to-your-career.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“To make your open house a success, here are a few tips to follow.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, &lt;strong&gt;utilize social media.&lt;/strong&gt; There are plenty of inexpensive advertising opportunities on Facebook and Instagram. Craigslist is another free source you can use. Also, start door knocking and invite the neighbors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lastly, on the day of the open house, &lt;strong&gt;make sure you have a sign-in sheet handy.&lt;/strong&gt; You want to record people’s information because—remember—you’re trying to get buyer leads. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to learn more tips for building a successful real estate business, I invite you to attend one of my business planning sessions or schedule a one-on-one strategy session. I look forward to hearing from you. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 14:53:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-hosting-an-open-house-is-a-great-start-to-your-career.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/why-hosting-an-open-house-is-a-great-start-to-your-career.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
